Register of the Papers of A. E. Dick Howard for the Virginia Commission for Constitutional Revision 1969-1971
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
Register of the Papers of A. E. Dick Howard for the Virginia Commission for Constitutional Revision 1969-1971
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
MSS 81-4
This collection documents the revision of Virginia's constitution from the appointment of the Commission on Constitutional Revision in 1968 to the adoption of the revision in November 1970. Professor A.E. Dick Howard served as Executive Director of the Commission and as director of Virginians for the Constitution, a bi-partisan coalition which publicized and promoted the revision.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Biographical/Historical Information
These files contain University of Virginia Law Professor A. E. Dick Howard's personal papers relating to the 1968 to 1971 revision of Virginia's constitution. Former Governor Albertis Harrison appointed Howard Executive Director of the Commission on Constitutional Revision (CCR) in February, 1968, and his papers document all the activities of the Commission. In the Final Report of the CCR (Box 35) is a detailed history of the Commission's work.
After his appointment as Executive Director, Howard undertook the formidable task of organizing and administering the work of the Commission. The Commissioners themselves were highly visible legal and political figures, chosen for their stature in the Commonwealth. Following a lengthy study of recent revisions in other states, Howard proposed a plan of operation and a timetable for the work of the CCR. Dividing critical substantive areas of the revision process among five committees, Howard and the Commissioners selected five special counsel to act as directors of each committee. The Counsel were chosen from the ranks of law professors at Virginia's four law schools, as well as outstanding private lawyers, and two Commissioners were assigned to each committee. Several at-large counsel provided general legal and political advice, and public views were solicited from all areas of the Commonwealth at a series of widely publicized open hearings.
Howard assigned student researchers to each committee, delegated areas of responsibility to the committee counsel, and compiled an extensive research bibliography on constitutional revision for the use of researchers and counsel. During the summer of 1968, student researchers turned out more than one hundred detailed topical memoranda pertaining to various aspects of the revision process. Each committee met privately, and late in the summer, the full Commission began to evaluate the work of the committees and discuss proposed revisions.
In the fall of 1968, the Executive Director began to collate the various proposals of the committees into a draft of the proposed revision. This draft was modified, re-written and organized by the Commissioners and the Executive Director, who wrote extensive commentaries on each proposed revision. By December the CCR had agreed on a full draft of its Final Report to the Governor, a completely revised Constitution.
After the CCR submitted its final report to Governor Mills Godwin in January 1969, Howard acted as Special Counsel to the Special Session of the General Assembly charged with amending the Howard-CCR Constitution in light of the CCR proposals. Virginia law required that amendments to the existing constitution be ratified by two sessions of the General Assembly, and then submitted to the people in the form of referenda. As Special Counsel, Howard interpreted the CCR proposals to the Assembly, attended committee meetings, met individually with Assembly members, provided constitutional advice, and finally re-wrote each proposed revision in terms acceptable to both houses of the General Assembly. The General Assembly formulated the proposed constitutional revisions into four amendments to the existing constitution, which were subsequently passed by the succeeding General Assembly in 1970.
In light of the previous popular rejections of proposed revised Constitutions in New York and Maryland, Governor Linwood Holton urged the formation of a privately funded organization to promote and publicize the proposed revisions. This organization, Virginians for the Constitution, a bi-partisan, broadly based coalition of concerned citizens and politicians, selected Professor Howard as its director. In this position he organized speakers' series, mailing lists, publicity campaigns and press cooperation for the referendum. Virginians for the Constitution succeeded in its goals, for in November, 1970, the voters overwhelmingly approved the revised Constitution, completing the three-year revision process.
Scope and Content Information
Howard's CCR papers (1968-1971) consisting of 37 boxes were donated the collection to the Archives in the summer of 1981.
The collection is generally in chronological order and is divided into seven series, reflecting divisions in the work of the Commission and in the later roles Howard played as counsel to the General Assembly and director of Virginians for the Constitution. Series I, Howard's files as Executive Director of the CCR, contains organizational memoranda, correspondence, minutes of meetings, and calendars relating to the Administration of the Commission. Series II documents the workings of each of the five subcommittees and contains research memoranda and drafts of the proposed substantive revisions. Research material, Series III, includes portions of other state Constitutions and complete texts of all public views submitted to the Commission. Series IV documents the drafting, revision and re-writing of the CCR's Final Report. Series V consists of Howard's files as Special Counsel to the 1969 Special Session of the General Assembly and contains minutes of committee meetings; Howard's calendar; drafts of resolutions, bills and proposed amendments; and correspondence relating to the Special Session. Series VI is composed of Howard's personal files as Director of Virginians for the Constitution and contains promotional brochures, press releases, speaking engagement records, and correspondence pertaining to the campaign. Series VII contains newspaper clippings gathered by the Virginia Press Association, which span the entire period of revision, 1968-1971; published writings of Howard relating to the revision process, as well as the Final Report and a tape recording of a radio broadcast of Virginians for the Constitution. Finally, there are numerous photographs of the Commission.
Contents List
- AEDH's Organizational Files
  - CCR Executive Director of Administrative Papers 1968 (Box 1)
    Areas of committee responsibility, preliminary reports on questions to explore by the subcommittees
  - CCR Executive Director Administrative Papers 1968, 4 folders (Box 1)
    Reports, proposals, lists, summaries, notes on commission's meetings, commentaries, etc
  - CCR Meetings 1968, 2 folders (Box 2)
    AEDH handwritten and typed notes
  - CCR Commissioners' Addresses 1968 (Box 2)
  - CCR Index n.d. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence with Commissioners
    - Albert V. Bryan 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - George M. Cochran 1968 (Box 2)
    - Ted Dalton 1968 (Box 2)
    - Colgate W. Darden 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Hardy C. Dillard 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Alexander M. Harmon 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Albertis S. Harrison 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Oliver W. Hill 1969-1971 (Box 2)
    - J. Sloan Kuykendall 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Davis Y. Paschall 1968-1972 (Box 2)
    - Lewis F. Powell 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence with CCR Counsel 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Thomas S. Currier 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - John F. Kay 1968-1971 (Box 2)
    - Peter W. Low 1968-1971 (Box 3)
    - Hullihen W. Moore 1971 (Box 3)
    - Jack H. Spain 1968-1971 (Box 3)
    - William F. Swindler 1968-1971 (Box 3)
    - Research Associates 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 3)
      Correspondence and curricula
    - Correspondence A 1968 (Box 3)
    - Accounts 1968-1969, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Advisors [Albertis S. Harrison Correspondence] 1968 (Box 3)
    - Agenda: April 5 and May 9 1968 (Box 3)
    - Archives 1969 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence B 1968-1970 (Box 3)
    - Bibliography 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - Bibliographical Data 1969 (Box 4)
    - Budget 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - Button, Robert Y. Attorney General 1968-1969 (Box 4)
      Correspondence and commentaries on Bill of Rights
    - Correspondence C 1968-1970 (Box 4)
    - March; CCR Report 1969 (Box 4)
      Commemorative booklets and correspondence
    - Citizen's Committees 1969 (Box 4)
    - Clippings Services 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - Code Commission 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - Computer 1968 (Box 4)
    - Conservation Bill of Rights 1968 (Box 4)
    - Constitution of Virginia 1902 (Box 4)
    - Consultants 1968 (Box 4)
    - Counsel 1968 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence D 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - Dicta Reports 1970 (Box 4)
    - Dissent (Minority Reports) 1969 (Box 4)
    - Duelling 1968 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence E 1968-1970 (Box 5)
    - Equipment 1968 (Box 5)
    - Essays on the Constitution 1969 (Box 5)
      Correspondence
    - Correspondence F 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Final Reports-Acknowledgements 1969 (Box 5)
    - Form Letters 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Forms: Tax and Exemptions 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence G 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - General Assembly 1970-1971 (Box 5)
    - Governor's Office Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence H 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Historians' Correspondence 1968 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence I 1968 (Box 5)
    - Index to Articles on Virginia Law n.d. (Box 5)
    - Correspondence J 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence K 1968-1970 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence L 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Lapsley, G. M. [Secy. to the Commission] 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Law Faculties in Virginia 1968 (Box 5)
    - League of Women Voters 1968 (Box 5)
    - Legislatures. CCSL [Citizens Conference on State Legislatures] 1969 (Box 5)
    - Letters of Appreciation 1969 (Box 5)
    - Letters to Newspaper Editors 1969 (Box 5)
    - Library 1968 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence M 1968-1970 (Box 5)
    - Mailing List Requests 1968 (Box 5)
    - Meetings 1968 (Box 5)
    - Michie Company 1969 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence N 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - National Municipal League 1968 (Box 5)
    - News Releases 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Newspaper Articles 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence O 1968 (Box 5)
    - Office 1968 (Box 5)
    - Orders for Commission Portrait 1968 (Box 5)
    - Oysters [sic.] Correspondence 1968 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence P 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Pennsylvania Legislative Data Processing Center 1968 (Box 6)
    - Pictures 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Presentation of Final Report 1969 (Box 6)
    - Press Briefing 1969 (Box 6)
    - Printers 1969 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence R 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Requests for Memoranda 1969 (Box 6)
    - Research Projects in Progress 1968 (Box 6)
    - Reservations 1968 (Box 6)
    - Resolution Creating Commission 1968 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence S 1968 (Box 6)
    - Secretarial Help 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Speaking Engagements (Commissioners and Counsel) 1969 (Box 6)
    - Statutes 1968 (Box 6)
    - Subcommittees 1968 (Box 6)
    - Summary of CCR Report 1969 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence T 1969 (Box 6)
    - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1968 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence V 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Van Schreeven, William [State Archivist] 1968 (Box 6)
    - Virginia State Bar Association 1968-1970 (Box 6)
    - Virginia Association of Counties 1967-1968 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence W 1968 (Box 6)
    - Wheeler, John P 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence Y 1968 (Box 6)
- Subcommittee Working Papers
  - Bill of Rights Subcommittee
    - Advisory Group on Bill Rights and Franchise 1968 (Box 7)
    - An Authoritative Version of the Constitution 1968 (Box 7)
    - Due Process 1968 (Box 7)
    - Research Materials 1968 (Box 7)
      Proposed Questions for Exploration; Form Citations; Research Memoranda; Form, Content and Designation of "working papers"
    - Swindler's Historical Material 1968 (Box 7)
    - Bill of Rights: Amendments, Future Cases 1945 (Box 7)
    - Bill of Rights: Correspondence, Memos, Reports on Meetings 1968 (Box 7)
    - Bill of Rights: General 1968 (Box 7)
    - Bill of Rights Research Memo: Irrational Classifications. Draft 1968 (Box 7)
    - Bill of Rights Working Papers. Political Rights, Propositions, etc. (Folder 1) 1968 (Box 7)
    - Bill of Rights Working Papers. Capital Punishment, Numbers of Jurors, Revisions, Research, and Drafts (Folder 2) 1968 (Box 8)
    - Educations: Correspondence, Memos 1968 (Box 8)
    - Education: Enforceability of Constitutional Language 1968 (Box 8)
    - Education: Research Materials 1968 (Box 8)
    - Education Memo: "Right to Education" 1968 (Box 8)
    - Education Working Papers 1968, 2 folders (Box 8)
      Memos, provisions from state constitutions, school fund, literary fund, public school authority, state aid to private schools, education articles
    - Education: Educational Advisory Group 1968 (Box 9)
      Correspondence and Report
    - Franchise: Federal Statutes 1968 (Box 9)
    - Franchise: Purging registered voter list; Form of ballots; Absentee ballots and the Electoral Vote. Registration Oaths 1968 (Box 9)
    - Franchise: Report and Memo. Qualifications for Office, Conflicts of Interest 1968 (Box 9)
    - Franchise Working Papers s, 9 (Box b)
      Qualifications of voters, qualifications to hold office, methods of voting, equal representations, etc.
    - Suffrage: Qualifications 1968 (Box 9)
      Research papers
    - Suffrage Working Papers 1968, 2 folders (Box 9)
      Minimum age, disqualification for duelling, residence requirements, suffrage registration, literacy tests, etc
    - Bill of Rights Subcommittee Blue Book (Box 9)
  - Legislative and Judicial Subcommittee
    - Judiciary: General 1968 (Box 9)
      Recommendations, list of court judges, correspondence, judicial article
    - Judiciary: Removal of Judges 1968 (Box 9)
    - Judicial Working Files. Peter Low's Files 1968, 2 folders (Box 9)
      Re: Court of criminal appeals, enforcement of canons of judicial ethics, disbarment proceedings, proposals, impeachment, etc.
    - Legislature: Annual Sessions, Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Legislature: Miscellaneous Correspondence and Research Material 1968 (Box 9)
    - Legislature Working Files. Peter Low's Files 1968, 4 folders (Box 11)
      Re: questions to explore, limitations of legislative power, requirements, working papers for commission's meetings, office-holding, analysis, articles, etc.
    - Legislature and Judicial Subcommittee Blue Book (Box 11)
  - Executive and State Administration Subcommittee
    - Administration: Articles V, X, and XI Working Files 1968 (Box 12)
    - Administration: Corporations Memoranda 1-15 1968 (Box 12)
    - Administration: Correspondence, Proposals 1968 (Box 12)
    - Administration: Preliminary Drafts of Articles V and XII. Executive Power and Corporations 1968 (Box 12)
    - Administration: Public Officers 1968 (Box 12)
    - Administration Working Files: Executive Compensation, Budget System, Bureau of Labor and Statistics, Civil Service System, etc. 1968 (Box 12)
    - Executive: Virginia Code and Constitutional Provisions for the Appointments, terms of office, removal and vacancies of state officers in the departments and agencies of the Executive Branch 1968 (Box 12)
    - Executive Working Papers 1968, 2 folders (Box 12)
      Succession to the office of Governor, gubernatorial tenure, executive clemency, governor's duties and powers
    - Corporations Working Papers. Article XII. Working papers #1 and 2 1968 (Box 13)
    - Executive and State Administration Blue Book (Box 13)
  - Local Government
    - Bonds Correspondence 1969 (Box 13)
    - Consolidation 1968 (Box 13)
    - Constitutional Officers 1968-1971 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, Memos, Reports 1968 (Box 13)
    - Debt 1968 (Box 13)
    - Metropolitan Government 1968 (Box 13)
    - Working Files 1968, 3 folders (Box 13)
      Revenue sources, Hahn report, liability of counties, local authorities, commission of local government, financing, local authorities, etc. and Working papers # 1 and 2
    - Local Government Blue Book (Box 13)
  - Taxation and Financial Subcommittee
    - Abutting Landowners 1968 (Box 14)
    - Assessment 1968 (Box 14)
    - Assessment Working Files 1968 (Box 14)
      Assessment of real and tangible personal property, of public service companies by the state corporation commission, etc
    - Bonds 1969 (Box 14)
    - Conforming Taxes 1969 (Box 14)
    - Corporations Drafts 1968 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence and Notes 1968 (Box 14)
    - Debt correspondence, newspaper articles 1968 (Box 14)
    - Debt Working Files 1968 (Box 14)
      Opinions of financial experts, debt in anticipation of collection on revenue, evidence of indebtedness, state debt limit, Virginia's need for modern debt provisions
    - Exemptions Correspondence 1968 (Box 14)
    - Exemptions Working Files 1968 (Box 14)
      Re: of household goods and personal effects, homesteads of the aged, air and water pollution; coal and mineral lands; industrial development; surrender of power to tax corporations, satute of limitations, collection and disposition of state revenue, taxation of railroads and canal companies
    - Revenue Bonds 1970 (Box 15)
      Correspondence, newspaper articles
    - State Corporation Commission 1968 (Box 15)
    - State Credit Lending 1968 (Box 15)
    - Taxation: Virginia Income Tax Study Commission Memorandum. Working Paper No. 1 1968 (Box 15)
    - Taxation 1968 (Box 15)
      Preliminary drafts; Working paper no. 1
    - Taxation Working Files 1968 (Box 15)
      Research, memos, correspondence
    - Taxation and Finance Subcommittee Blue Book (Box 15)
- Research Materials--State Constitutions and Public Views (See also Series VIII)
  - State Constitutions Correspondence 1968
    - Alabama 1968-1971 (Box 16)
    - Alaska 1968 (Box 16)
    - Arizona 1968 (Box 16)
    - Arkansas 1968-1975 (Box 16)
    - California 1968 (Box 16)
    - Colorado 1968 (Box 16)
    - Connecticut 1968 (Box 16)
    - Delaware 1968 (Box 16)
    - Florida 1968 (Box 16)
    - Georgia 1968 (Box 16)
    - Hawaii 1968 (Box 16)
    - Idaho 1968 (Box 16)
    - Illinois 1968 (Box 16)
    - Indiana 1968 (Box 16)
    - Iowa 1968 (Box 16)
    - Kansas 1968 (Box 16)
    - Kentucky 1968 (Box 16)
    - Louisiana 1968 (Box 16)
    - Maine 1968 (Box 16)
    - Maryland 1967-1968, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Massachusetts 1968 (Box 16)
    - Michigan 1968 (Box 16)
    - Minnesota 1968 (Box 16)
    - Mississippi 1968 (Box 16)
    - Missouri 1968 (Box 16)
    - Montana 1972-1974 (Box 16)
    - Nebraska 1968-1970 (Box 16)
    - Nevada 1968 (Box 16)
    - New Hampshire 1968 (Box 17)
    - New Jersey 1968 (Box 17)
    - New Mexico 1968 (Box 17)
    - New York 1968, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - North Carolina 1968-1969 (Box 17)
    - North Dakota 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Ohio 1968-1972 (Box 17)
    - Oklahoma 1968 (Box 17)
    - Pennsylvania 1968-1969 (Box 17)
    - Rhode Island 1968 (Box 17)
    - South Carolina 1972 (Box 17)
    - South Dakota 1972 (Box 17)
    - Tennessee 1968 (Box 17)
    - Texas 1968 (Box 17)
    - Utah 1968-1970 (Box 17)
    - Vermont 1968 (Box 17)
    - Washington 1968 (Box 17)
    - West Virginia 1968 (Box 17)
    - Wisconsin 1968 (Box 17)
    - Wyoming 1968 (Box 17)
    - Public Views Correspondence and Organization 1968 (Box 17)
    - Public Hearings and Communications 1968 (Box 17)
    - Public Hearings Notes and Summaries 1968 (Box 17)
    - Public Views: Documents #1-214 1968, 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Public Views-submitted after final report of CCR 1969 (Box 18)
- Drafts and Final Copies of the Commission's Report and Commentary
  - Commentary to accompany text of draft Constitution 1968 (Box 19)
    Introduction and complete draft
  - Deleted pages of Commentary [to education article] n.d. (Box 19)
  - Drafts of Commentaries to Constitutional Articles:
    - Bill of Rights: Art. I 1968 (Box 19)
    - Franchise: Art. II 1968 (Box 19)
    - Division of Powers: Arts. III and XII 1968 (Box 19)
    - Legislature: Art IV 1968 (Box 19)
    - Executive and State Administration: Art. V 1968 (Box 19)
    - Judiciary: Art. VI 1968 (Box 19)
    - Local Government: Art. VII 1968 (Box 19)
    - Education: Art. VIII 1968 (Box 19)
    - Corporations: Art. IX 1968 (Box 19)
    - Taxation: Art. X 1968 (Box 19)
    - Conservation: Art XI 1968 (Box 19)
    - Schedule 1968 (Box 19)
    - Replacement Pages for Certain Sections of Revised Constitution 1968 (Box 19)
    - Final Draft Proposed Constitution and Commentary 1968 (Box 19)
      Introduction, Title Page, Text of Proposed Revisions
    - December; Final Draft of Proposed Constitution: Arts. I-VI 1968 (Box 19)
    - December; Final Draft of Proposed Constitution: Arts. VII-XII 1968, 5 folders (Box 21)
    - Final Report-Mailing List 1968-1969 (Box 21)
    - Final Report-Billing 1969 (Box 21)
    - Requests for Commission Report: A-C 1969, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Requests for Commission Report: D-P 1969, 8 folders (Box 22)
    - Requests for Commission Report: R-Z 1969, 5 folders (Box 23)
    - Final Report-Postcard Replies 1969 (Box 23)
    - Out-of-state Requests for Final Report 1969 (Box 23)
    - Letters Replies to Requests for Commission Report 1969 (Box 23)
- AEDH's Files and Transcript Proceedings for the Special Session of the General Assembly
  - Transcripts of the Special Session of the General Assembly, including one bound volume of the Offical Senate Journal of the 1969 extra session 1969 (Box 24)
  - Special Session of the General Assembly: AEDH Calendar 1969 (Box 25)
  - Special Session of the General Assembly: AEDH Committee Notes 1969 (Box 2 folders)
  - Special Session of the State Legislature: Arts. I-VII 1969, 7 folders (Box 25)
  - Special Session of the State Legislature: Arts. VIII-XII and Schedule 1969, 7 folders (Box 26)
  - Special Session of State Legislature--Commission Members 1969 (Box 26)
  - Conferee Committees 1969 (Box 26)
  - Deletion of Articles 1969 (Box 26)
  - General-with Index 1969 (Box 26)
  - Hearing Tapes 1969 (Box 26)
  - Governor Godwin's Office 1969 (Box 26)
  - Parallel Tables 1969 (Box 26)
  - Resolutions and Amendments 1969 (Box 27)
  - Status of Joint Resolutions 1969, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Drafting-Comparison of Resolutions of House and Senate 1969 (Box 27)
  - Select Committee 1969 (Box 27)
  - Separate Questions n.d. (Box 27)
  - Summary of Actions Taken 1969 (Box 27)
  - April 25 Meetings of House and Senate 1969 (Box 27)
  - General Assembly Session 1970 (Box 27)
- "Virginians for the Constitution" Campaign Files
  - Virginians for the Constitution: Draft Resolutions 1970 (Box 28)
  - Mailing Lists 1971, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Moore's Memo on "Form of Ballot" 1968 (Box 28)
  - Office Memoranda 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-A.E.D. Howard 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-Commentaries 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-Correspondence 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-Incorporation 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-Opposition 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-Speakers Notes 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-Television 1970 (Box 28)
  - Promotion-Western Community College Project 1970 (Box 28)
  - Speaking Engagements 1970, 4 folders (Box 29)
  - Virginia Votes for a New Constitution 1973 (Box 29)
- Newspaper Clippings and Published Material
  - Newspaper Clippings 1968-1971, 24 folders (Box 30-34)
  - CCR Published Materials
    - "Summary of Recommendations to the Governor and the General Assembly of Virginia" (Box 35)
    - "Summary of the Proposed Constitutional Amendments Approved by the General Assembly..." (Box 35)